

Billstein M. Lelatobur

in f

I am twenty-two years old. I am a graduate of S1 Informatics Engineering from Satya Wacana Christian University. I am confident that my qualifications and skills can make a significant contribution to the company. I am a person who can work well as part of a team and alone. I am also a hard worker, and eager to learn

Web Developer



Kota Ambon, Maluku, Indonesia

Work Experience

Web Developer • PT Compro Kotak Inovasi



September 2020 - December 2020

Here I am with a team developing an Ecommerce Web for the company, using the PHP programming language with the Laravel framework

Web Developer • UKSW, Faculty of Information Technology



February 2021 - June 2021

Here I am making a Web for Borrowing Goods for my faculty, using the PHP programming language with the Laravel framework

Education

THIS AMERICAN	Universitas Kristen Satya Wacana Teknik Informatika	2017 - 2022
	SMA Negeri Letwurung IPA	2015 - 2017
	SMPN 1 Letti Moa Lakor IPA	2012 - 2014
	SD Inpres Serwaru	2006 - 2011

Skil

- Laravel PHP Framework
- PHP
- html + css + javascript + jQuery + MySql

Language

- English Menengah
- Indonesian Bahasa Ibu